tastyblogsnack.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy – iJustine

Welcome to iJustine, a website (the "Website") licensed by Flutter, Inc, ("Flutter", "We" or "Us"). This Privacy Policy (the "Privacy Policy") along with the Terms of Use provides the terms and conditions governing your use of this Website. Flutter provides intriguing web content, ideas, images, advertising and messages about news, entertainment, health and culture for its community platforms, brands, partners and advertisers.

Your privacy is important to Flutter. Therefore, we have developed a Privacy Policy that covers how we collect, use, disclose, transfer and store your information. Please take a moment to familiarize yourself with our Privacy Policy. By using Flutter you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy also applies to users that have agreed to receive e-mail marketing from Flutter and joint marketing advertisers that collaborate with Flutter, whether via email, on third party websites, via co-registration or otherwise.

#### 1\. Collection and Use of Personal Information

You may be asked to provide your personal information anytime you are in contact with Flutter or an affiliated company, when you use our Website. Flutter and its affiliates may share this personal information with each other and use it consistent with this Privacy Policy. They may also combine it with other information to provide and improve our products, services, content and advertising. You agree to provide information, which shall be true, correct and accurate, based on your knowledge. You may amend, alter or require deletion of certain details of your information by contacting the Website at the contact details provided, below.

Your information may also be stored and processed in a country other than the one where you use the Website. For purposes of sharing or disclosing data in accordance with the Privacy Policy, Flutter reserves the right to transfer your information outside of your country. By using the Website, you consent to any such transfer of your information outside of your country and also within Flutter's affiliates, subsidiaries and partners whose personnel and subcontractors, shall have access to the same provided they have agreed to abide by the terms of the Privacy Policy and the applicable data protection laws. To make sure your personal information is secure; we communicate our privacy and security guidelines to Flutter employees and enforce privacy safeguards within Flutter.

This Website is not directed towards minors. We do not knowingly collect personal information from any person who is under 18 years. If we learn that we have collected the personal information of a person below the age of 18 years, we will take steps to delete the information within a reasonable time frame. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided the Website with any information without their consent, he or she should contact Flutter at the contact details provided in this Privacy Policy. You as an adult should be rightfully aware, that by entering information willfully and knowingly, you have entered into a binding contract with the Website.

Given below are some examples of the type of personal information that Flutter may collect and how we may use it. You are advised to read the same.

#### What personal information we collect:

When you submit information upon registration, we may collect a variety of information, including your name, password, mailing address, phone number, email address and contact preferences, including any other usage and interaction details with Flutter, or a Flutter affiliated company. You may be required to update your information from time to time for which you shall be sent notifications.

#### How we use your personal information:

  * The personal information we collect allows us to keep you posted on Flutter's latest product announcements, software updates and upcoming events, including confirmations, invoices, technical notices, updates, security alerts and support and administrative messages. It also helps us to improve our services, content and advertising. If you do not want to be on our mailing list, you can opt out at anytime by updating your preferences on the Website.
  * We also use personal information to help us develop, deliver, and improve our products, services, content, and advertising and to personalize and improve your experience.
  * From time to time, we may use your personal information to send important notices, such as communications and changes to our terms, conditions and policies. Since, this information is important to your interaction with Flutter, you cannot opt out of receiving these communications.
  * We may also use personal information for internal purposes such as auditing, data analysis and research to improve Flutter's products, services and customer communications.
  * To register for an account with us to build an application.

#### 2\. Collection and Use of Non-Personal Information

We also collect non-personal information (data in a form that does not permit direct association with any specific individual). We may collect, use, transfer and disclose non-personal information for any purpose.

Given below are some examples of non-personal information that we collect and how we may use it:

  * We may collect information such as industry, language, pin code, area code, unique device identifier, location and the time zone, where a Flutter product is used so that we can better understand customer behavior and improve our products, services and advertising.
  * We also may collect information regarding customer activities on our Website and from our other products and services. This information may be aggregated and used to help us provide more useful information to our customers and to understand which parts of our Website, products and services are of most interest. Such aggregated data shall be considered as non-personal information for the purposes of this Privacy Policy.

In the event we combine any non-personal information along with any personal information, the combined information will be treated as personal information for as long as it remains combined.

#### 3\. Cookies and Other Technologies

Flutter's Website, online services, email messages and advertisements may use "cookies" and other technologies such as pixel tags. These technologies help us better understand user behavior, tells us which parts of our Website users have visited and facilitates and measures the effectiveness of advertisements and web searches. A cookie is a small piece of information that a website can send to your browser which may then be stored on your computer's hard drive. It acts as an anonymous tag that identifies your computer, but not you personally. Cookies have the ability to store information about web pages viewed and the advertisements viewed or clicked. For registered customers, cookies can also save user information and screen preferences. We treat information collected by cookies and other technologies as non-personal information.

However, to the extent that Internet Protocol (IP) addresses or similar identifiers are considered personal information by law, we also treat these identifiers as personal information.

Flutter and its affiliates use cookies and other technologies in mobile advertising services to control the number of times you see a given ad, deliver ads that relate to your interests and measure the effectiveness of advertising campaigns. This helps Flutter improve the quality of its service by storing user preferences, improves search results and advertisement selection and tracks user trends. If you do not want to receive advertisements with this level of relevance, you can opt out by contacting Flutter through the contact details provided below. However, if you choose to opt out, you will continue to receive the same number of advertisements, but they may be less relevant because they will not be based on your interests. You may still see advertisements related to the content on a web page or in an application or based on other non-personal information. This opt out applies only to Flutter advertising services and does not affect interest-based advertising from other advertising networks.

Flutter and its affiliates also use cookies and other technologies to remember personal information when you use our Website, online services and applications. Our goal, in these cases, is to make your experience with Flutter more convenient and personal.

If you want to disable cookies you can modify your settings on your browser in order to reject automatic acceptance of cookie. Please check with your provider to find out how to disable cookies. Please note that certain features of the Website may not be available once cookies are disabled.

We gather some information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, browser type and language, internet service provider (ISP), referring and exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp and click-stream data. We use this information to understand and analyze trends, to administer the Website, to learn about user behavior on the Website and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. Flutter and its affiliates may use this information in marketing and advertising services as well.

Pixel tags, also known as a clear GIF or web beacon, are invisible tags placed on certain pages of our website but not on your computer. When you access these pages, pixel tags generate a generic notice of that visit. They usually work in conjunction with cookies, registering when a particular computer visits a particular page. If you turn off cookies, the pixel tag will simply detect an anonymous website visit. Pixel tags enables Flutter to send email messages in such a format that customer can read and they tell us whether the email has been opened by the customer. We may use this information to reduce or eliminate messages sent to customers.

#### 4\. Disclosure to Third Parties

At times Flutter may make certain personal information available to strategic partners that work with Flutter to provide products and services, or that help Flutter market to customers, such as a credit card processing company to bill you for services or an email service provider to send out emails on our behalf. Personal information will only be shared by Flutter to provide or improve our products, services and advertising, however, it will not be shared with third parties for their marketing purposes. You shall be contacted for a confirmation on any of your personal information being shared with a third party and if you wish not to share any such information with the third party, Flutter shall respect such request.

#### 5\. Information Sharing

Notwithstanding anything contained to the contrary, your information may be shared by Flutter:

    * (i) with its legal counsel/s or upon a law enforcement agency's request or in response to a legal process (for instance, in response to a court order or a subpoena);
    * (ii) during investigations, for prevention of any illegal activities or suspected fraud;
    * (iii) situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person;
    * (iv) violations of any of the terms of the Policy and to verify or enforce compliance with the policies governing the Website or its Applications and applicable laws or as otherwise required or permitted by law or as consistent with the legal requirements of United States of America;
    * (v) to operate its systems properly including sharing with Flutter's affiliates; or
    * (vi) to protect other Website users; or
    * (vii) with third party subcontractors solely for the purpose of or in connection with the services, who are contractually bound to protect your information from unauthorized use or transfer.

Additionally, in the event of reorganization, bankruptcy, merger, or sale of company assets, financing, or acquisition of all or a portion of our business to another company, we may transfer any and all personal information we collect to the relevant third party. You will have the opportunity to opt out of any such transfer if the new entity's planned processing of your information differs materially from that set forth in this.

#### 6\. Security

The security of your personal information is important to us. Flutter takes precautions, including administrative, technical and physical measures, to safeguard your personal information against loss, theft and misuse, as well as against unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card numbers) on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). This Website has various electronic, procedural and physical security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of information, or any accidental loss, destruction or damage to data. When you submit your information via the Website, your information is protected through Flutter 's security systems. There may be instances where Flutter requires proof of identity before disclosing any of your information to you. You agree to be responsible to protect the security of your username and password and other registration details, if any.

Flutter may create links to other websites. You are requested to be aware that Flutter does not provide any personally identifiable information to such other websites and that it is not responsible for the privacy practices of third parties. You agree that Flutter cannot control these links and Flutter shall not be responsible for any use of such websites. If you have any questions about the security at the Website, you may contact us. Please be aware, however, that despite our efforts, no security measures are impenetrable.

#### 7\. Integrity and Retention of Data

Flutter makes it easy for you to keep your personal information accurate, complete and up to date. We will retain your personal information and any data for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law.

#### 8\. Modification

Flutter reserves the right to amend this Privacy Policy at any time. The policies, as and how modified, shall be updated on the Website and the same shall be notified on the Website. We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy whenever you visit our Website s to understand how your personal information is used.

#### 9\. Contact for any Questions

In case, you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, or this Website, or your dealings with this Website, you may contact a representative of Flutter by e-mailing us at help@flutter.co.

#### 10\. Unsubscribe

The Website provides the user the opportunity to stop receiving communications from Flutter. In order to do this, you need to send an e-mail to help@flutter.co.
